<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ens on baoqdau</title>
    <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ens on baoqdau</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 07:40:51 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Good</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 07:40:51 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/good/</guid>
      <description>Understand you Moods: You feel the Way you think Every bad feelings you have is the result of your distorted negative thinking. Intense negative thinking always accompanies a depressive episode, or any painful emotion for that matter.
 Every time I become depressed, I feel as if I have been hit with a sudden cosmic jolt, and begin to see things differently. The change can come within less than an hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laws of Human Nature</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/laws-of-human-nature/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 03:20:31 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/laws-of-human-nature/</guid>
      <description>We have to deal with people who initially appear charming or confident, brimming with ideas and enthusiasm, and we fall under their spell. Only when it is too late that we discover that their confidence is irrational and their ideas ill-conceived. What inevitably happens in these situations is that we are caught off guard, not expecting such behavior. Often these types will hit us with elaborate cover stories to justify their actions, or blame handy scapegoat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastery</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 15:25:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/mastery/</guid>
      <description>By nature, we humans shrink from anything that seems possibly painful or overtly difficult. We bring this natural tendency to our practice of any skill. Once we grow dept at some aspect of this skill, generally one that comes more easily to us, we prefer to practice this element over and over. Our skill becomes lopsided as we avoid our weaknesses. Knowing that in our practice we can let down our guard, since we are not being watched or under pressure to perform, we bring to this a kind of dispersed attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Skinny on Time Management</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/time-management1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 13:12:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/time-management1/</guid>
      <description>being busy There are times in most of our lives when being busy is a refuge. By keeping ourselves busy, we avoid finding the quiet time needed reflect on difficult choices. We know that we are in a situation that needs to change and yet, we create busyness to avoid making a hard decision.
Life is not fair  there are factors and events beyond your control that will impact how your life plays out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organized Mind</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/organized-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 15:00:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/organized-mind/</guid>
      <description>our brains are evolved to focus on one thing at a time
  attention is a limited-capacity resource. something can grab your attention automatically, usually something salient to your survival, with evolutionary origins.
  if we have a filter for
  attention overload as a serious problem
  we&amp;rsquo;re expected to do shadow work - the work of the companies for them.
     have you ever sat in an airplan or train, just staring out the window with nothing to read, looking at nothing in particular?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muscle</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/muscle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 13:08:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/muscle/</guid>
      <description>i can build muscle in a calorie deficit
build muscle:  water protein: 1g of protein per pound of weight energy: 3500 cal/lb of fat training stimulus:  training tips  warm up with light cardio. should be sweating a little bit before starting.  train the hardest exercises first  squats compounds first then isolation  time your set  time under tension is more important:40 seconds for hypertrophy   work rest ratio  3:1 or 5:1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defining Decade</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/defining-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 14:45:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/defining-decade/</guid>
      <description>resilient people are usually very likeable. clients with the toughest family backgrounds know the least about how to get what they want in love.
why people choose cohabitation women want better access to love. men want easier access to sex.
experiences   high school and our twenties are the only time when we have the most self-defining memories
  adolescence is the time of our first attempt to form life stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 16:40:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/principles/</guid>
      <description>dont confuse goals with desires
most problems are potential improvements list my problems.
if i cant identify my problems thats because either i lack the skill or lack the will :)
the problems are harsh reality, very painful to look at. so i cope my subconsciously put them out of sight to make them out of mind
i defintely worry about appearing to not have problems than about not achieving my desired results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Class War</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/note/class-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 13:26:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/note/class-war/</guid>
      <description>Excerpts from American Affairs&#39; The Real Class War. Note that this post is literally me taking notes (more like copying verbatim) of what the author wrote and I have absolutely no rights to the material provided. Don&amp;rsquo;t @ me.
 The working class has experienced economic stagnation and precarity, and even life expectancy in the US, as well as ower family stability and civic engagement. Social mobility has declined, while inequality has widened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I feel</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/cycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 16:30:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/cycle/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s meta, but I feel like no matter I do, I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to feel like how I want to feel.
Not that I have achieved a lot and feel empty afterwards. Full disclaimer, I have not achieved a single thing that I wanted to do this year. It&amp;rsquo;s sad and pathetic but it&amp;rsquo;s also enlightening, I guess.
It&amp;rsquo;s enlightening in a way that most people I&amp;rsquo;ve met feel this way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>on Lee Kuan Yew</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/funny-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 11:45:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/funny-thing/</guid>
      <description>I found myself thinking about what Lee Kuan Yew had to say about many things a lot recently. While I know close to nothing about him, I can imagine that most of his thoughts and actions stemmed from a systemic and practical approach.
I remember reading him stating that while he takes a certain liking to some ideas, he is only interested in what works in real life. This Machiavellian approach to problems reminds me of one of Charlie Munger&amp;rsquo;s lessons in life: avoid extremely intense ideology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ah Here We Go Again</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/ah-here-we-go-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 18:22:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/ah-here-we-go-again/</guid>
      <description>Hello world. Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m going to try to blog again. From my experience from past attempts, I can&amp;rsquo;t keep up with writing essays if I only treat it as a &amp;lsquo;feels good&amp;rsquo; activity when I procrastinate. Now that I know better, I will actually put self-imposed deadlines to churn out content for this blog.
Who knows what to make of this decision. I&amp;rsquo;m in part hopeful that I will try to do my research and write interesting articles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/overconfidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/overconfidence/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
