<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>baoqdau</title>
    <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on baoqdau</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 16:52:44 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.banhtrang.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rilke</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/poem/rilke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 16:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/poem/rilke/</guid>
      <description>I am to alone in the world, and not alone enough to make every moment holy I am too tiny in this world, and not tiny enough just to lie before you like a thing, shrewd and secretive I want my own will, and I want simply to be with my will, as it goes toward action, and in the silent, sometimes hardly moving times when something is coming near</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seduction</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/seduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 16:26:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/seduction/</guid>
      <description>Charismatic what is it?  has little to do with an exciting physical appearance of colorful personality: qualities that elicit short-term interst. clear vision, a quality of single-mindedness, and practical skills can be devastatingly charsmatic, provided it is matched with some success. it is an illusion in they eyes of those who see you as having what they lack. this is the guru effect. the aura you are after is not the fiery one of most charismatics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Addiction</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/addiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 12:55:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/addiction/</guid>
      <description>What am I addicted to  Hearthstone: Game Tiktok: social media Pornhub: porn feeling insecure   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowbanks</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/poem/snowbanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 16:24:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/poem/snowbanks/</guid>
      <description>Those great sweeps ofsnow that stop suddenly six feet from the house . . . Thoughts that go so far. The boy gets out ofhigh school and reads no more books; The son stops calling home. The mother puts down her rolling pin and makes no more bread. And the wife looks at her husband one night at a party) and loves him no more. The energy leaves the wine) and the minister falls leaving the church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be a Man</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/be-a-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 15:49:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/be-a-man/</guid>
      <description>What does it mean when a man falls in love with aradient face across the room? Instead of pursuing the woman and trying to get her alone, away from her husband, he needs to go alone himself, perhaps to a mountain cabin, for three months, write poetry, canoe down a river, and dream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prefrontal Training</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/prefrontal-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 16:21:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/prefrontal-training/</guid>
      <description>Dos Donts  get drunk: alcohol interferes with the ability of prefrontal cortex neurons to communicate with one another, by disrupting dopamine receptors and blocking a particular kind of neuron called an NMDA receptor. heavy drinkers also experience the frontal lobe system souble whammy: they lose certain capabilties, such as impulse control or motor coordination or the ability to drive safely, but they arent aware that theyve lost them. overgrowth of dopaminergic neurons in the frontal lobes leads to autism, which mimics fontal lobe damage to some degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My grocery from anabolic cookbook</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/diet/anabolic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 15:09:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/diet/anabolic/</guid>
      <description>Grocery Misc  Pam oil spray guar gum onion powder garlic salt grounded beef as lean as possible tomato  wrap for kitchen counter   protein  liquid muscle egg whites high protein wrap  Recipes Blueberries protein pancakes  In a blender:  4 cups egg white 8 bread slices 1 tbsp xanthan/guar gum let them sit for an hour  in a pan:  spray pam then literally pour the blended concoction into the pan  Wraps    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organized Mind</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/organized-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 15:00:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/organized-mind/</guid>
      <description>our brains are evolved to focus on one thing at a time
  attention is a limited-capacity resource. something can grab your attention automatically, usually something salient to your survival, with evolutionary origins.
  if we have a filter for
  attention overload as a serious problem
  we&amp;rsquo;re expected to do shadow work - the work of the companies for them.
     have you ever sat in an airplan or train, just staring out the window with nothing to read, looking at nothing in particular?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back Propagation</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/back-propagation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 20:40:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/back-propagation/</guid>
      <description>what is k-fold cross-validation.?????</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 14:02:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/happiness/</guid>
      <description>most of us are conditioned to devalue happiness right from childhood.
 we should try to not get distracted from making happiness-enhancing decisions  7 sins, 7 good habits prioritizing, but not pursuing, happiness chasing superiority  as children, we are exposed to feedback that tells us whether we are superior or inferior to others around us. consider the impact of failing to acquire a girlfriend or boyfriend when everyone else has one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Date</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/daily/nov30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 13:54:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/daily/nov30/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/health/stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 21:31:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/health/stress/</guid>
      <description>[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lkgR9EgMfe8](ADAPTOGENS EXPLAINED: Ginseng, Ashwagandha, Rhodiola + Science of Stress)
Panax Ginseng </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unscripted</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/lifestyle/unscripted/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 22:22:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/lifestyle/unscripted/</guid>
      <description>there are two time types i can manipulate: freee time and indentured time.
free time is the time I own. and it&amp;rsquo;s the only time that&amp;rsquo;s important. NOBODY has a cliam on it. I do what I want: sleep in, write, read, whatever warms my heart.
Follow SCRIPTED protocol and ypu&amp;rsquo;re locked into a shitty deal where free time is automatically presumed to exist only on the weekends
indentured time is time soneone else owns: school, studying, work, traffic, my biz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Love</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/relationship/getting-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 20:34:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/relationship/getting-love/</guid>
      <description>we all started out life whole and vital. To one degree or another, we were all wounded by our caretakers&#39; intrusiveness or neglect. We experienced a primitive anxiety: the world is not a safe place. When we are adults, capable of keeping ourselves fed and warm and dry. When our partners are hostile or unhelpful, a silent alarm is triggered deep in our brains that fills us with the fear of death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/book/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 13:36:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/book/</guid>
      <description>Plot: female main character changes from a naive and physically weak character to a strong, both physically and mentally.
 Circle Madelaine Miller  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tidy</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/lifestyle/tidy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 23:18:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/lifestyle/tidy/</guid>
      <description>discarding all at once intensely and completely tidy in the right order  do not even think of putting things away until i have finished the process of discarding  visualize my destination  imagine what it would be like to live in a clutter free space visualization aid: look at interior decorating magazines  the fuck this is pseudodeep  why i want to design my home that way. after a few rounds of recursive quasi-scientific soul searching im supposed to find out that the point of doing this is to be happy  selection criterion: joy  we should be choosing what we want to keep, not what we want to get rid of take each item in one&amp;rsquo;s hand and ask if this spark joy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 15:46:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/s/</guid>
      <description>I currently am a shitty person and I need to change this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relationship Cure</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/relationship/relationship-cure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 10:13:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/relationship/relationship-cure/</guid>
      <description>in relationships, if both parties are willing to hang in there, pay attention, and change direction when we make mistakes, we can improve the relationship.
step one: look at my bids   what makes marriages succeed or fail? self-disclosure: a person&amp;rsquo;s willingness to reveal his or her most guarded, personal thoughts and experiences to another person.
  &amp;lsquo;after collecting and viewing hundereds of hours of videotape, i found very few examples of self-disclosure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lift</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/lifestyle/lift/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 23:54:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/lifestyle/lift/</guid>
      <description>best 3 chest exercises: bench press incline dumbbell, remember to bring the dumbbells together
cardio  jumping jacks burpees bicycles ins outs open close shoulder to shoulder high knees  shoulder  reverse peck deck: side lateral raises seated overhead press  10 reps min
leg  smith machines: normal + chair squat + backward squat preacher shrimp dance step on one plate, weights on shoulder, squat down then stand up in the opposite direction smith machine calf raises, with plates 15 lunge while criss crossing kettlebells smith machine jumping lunge push smith machine with balls on your feet one legged squat jump over bench criss crossing on bench   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Minimalism</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/lifestyle/dig-min/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 16:31:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/lifestyle/dig-min/</guid>
      <description>Principles of digital minimalism clutter is costly optimization is important Thoreau economics The cost of a thing is the amount of life required to be exchanged for it immediately or in the long run.
radical rethinking of the consumerist culture.
 who could justify trading a lifetime of stress and backbreaking labor for better &amp;lsquo;stuff&amp;rsquo; Thoreau&amp;rsquo;s new economics was devaloped in an industrial age, but his insigts apply to our life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minigoal</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/lifestyle/goalpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 16:31:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/lifestyle/goalpost/</guid>
      <description>Most important: track how I spend my time digitally fix arbtt and see where I am on the productivity scale brother Completely stop using Tiktok yikes
stop playing mobile games now the question is. what am i going to do next. question  when do i play games? only when i get home. why? is it because my house has a relaxational aspect to it? now how do I stop compulsively gaming?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calorie</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/diet/calorie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 23:46:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/diet/calorie/</guid>
      <description>How many calories  upper ceiling: 3000 lose fat too fast youll lose muscle too  its better to lose weight slowly  youre losing 1% of your bodyweight a week   vitamin b6 H selective food sources of vitamin B6
chickpeas
beef liver
tuna Yellowfin fresh cooked
chicken breast
breakfast cereals
potatoes boiled
turkey
banana</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geneuinely in love with what im doing</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/personality/love-doing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 19:57:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/personality/love-doing/</guid>
      <description>no struggle to stay focused talk about the good things other people do, instead of talking about other people enjoy my time at work think about winning instead of surviving excited about what im doing hardly ever watch the clock view success in terms of fulfullment and gratification help others without thinking have freinds at work find my passion do many things stay true to myself focus on myself let go of fear how</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Esteem</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/personality/self-esteem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 19:57:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/personality/self-esteem/</guid>
      <description>If you lack the courage to live the life you really wnt, you&amp;rsquo;re going to be chronically disappointed in yourself
keep my promises to myself  people with low self-esteem are very good at keeping their promises to other people and very bad at keeping promises to themselves  choose good career path because society admires  choose to marry someone because they know their family would approve  true self-esteem comes from balancing the wants and needs of others with the wants and needs of myself  i need a solid founation of keeping promises to myself   spend more time with people i genuiunely like   i am the average of the five people i spend the most time with</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charm</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/relationship/charm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 19:16:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/relationship/charm/</guid>
      <description>The art of being engaged  Presence in the moment bruh im interest in looking cool instead of being cool attraction can only happens when both partners are being themselves  jump into the current environment
9 traits of charmers have authenticity  no facade openly opinionated embrace your individuality because you respect and love yourself  having fun  literally not  down to earth  trying to show that you&amp;rsquo;re better means youre insecure be vulnerable confidence is putting yourself up to rejection just to stay true to yourself  take interests in others  takes special interest in the person in front of you  effortlessly being intimate with the other person  work to make that person feels special  try to throw the wall away  rebellious polite and courteous    quick-witted    graceful  interacting with your environment in a harmonious way  passionate about something  literally the love for life  most </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>effective leader</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/eff-leader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 15:27:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/eff-leader/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 15:27:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/python/</guid>
      <description>Check if conda exists: conda list
okay so im having a massive problem with the way fastai library works. apparently we need bing&amp;rsquo;s image search api in order for this whole thing to work but bing just chnaged their endpoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/daily/nov21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 15:21:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/daily/nov21/</guid>
      <description> Lift with the new system Setup fastai core Buy cheese tofu   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charm</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/personality/charm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 14:53:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/personality/charm/</guid>
      <description>Tease this is to lift others up. not to let them down. compliments in disguise.
make fun of others&#39; superficial traits  saying the exact opposite of what he feels  shouldnt be  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muscle</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/muscle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 13:08:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/muscle/</guid>
      <description>i can build muscle in a calorie deficit
build muscle:  water protein: 1g of protein per pound of weight energy: 3500 cal/lb of fat training stimulus:  training tips  warm up with light cardio. should be sweating a little bit before starting.  train the hardest exercises first  squats compounds first then isolation  time your set  time under tension is more important:40 seconds for hypertrophy   work rest ratio  3:1 or 5:1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diet</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/diet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 13:06:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/diet/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 2</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/dl/l2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 14:20:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/dl/l2/</guid>
      <description>2 sets of books. fastbooks to learn. the other for experiment
dog cat dataset  tags contain dog and cat breeds create category: classification regression: predict one or more numeric quantities?  different applications  diagnosing viruses  terminology  mostly in the book  valid_pct: take a portion of the training dataset and put it asidefor testing purpose
  avoid overfitting
  cnn_learner(,(resnet34: resnet architecture, 34 layers, good for image recognition), metrics=error_rate, epoch: what we call when we look at every single image once?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 1</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/dl/l1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 19:16:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/dl/l1/</guid>
      <description>didactic approach deep learning is a type of neural network.
top down approach: see the big picture first. will get more technical at time goes by.
software fastai. pytorch: not designed for beginner&amp;rsquo;s friendliness.
a layered api 1  literally overloaded methods free factoring and  jupyter  server: backbone of my code everytime i run something it updates the server&amp;rsquo;s state  questionnaires at the end  read first: do all of them before moving to the next chapter  first notebook  error rate of 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overconfidence</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/overconfidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 17:04:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/overconfidence/</guid>
      <description>how to get over overconfidence always be learning beware beginnings slow down  fast decisions are generally more biased decisions   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defining Decade</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/defining-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 14:45:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/defining-decade/</guid>
      <description>resilient people are usually very likeable. clients with the toughest family backgrounds know the least about how to get what they want in love.
why people choose cohabitation women want better access to love. men want easier access to sex.
experiences   high school and our twenties are the only time when we have the most self-defining memories
  adolescence is the time of our first attempt to form life stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Less Traveled</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/road-less-traveled/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 19:45:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/road-less-traveled/</guid>
      <description>we all have maps. a comprehensive understanding of the world. transference is the problem of using our simplistic childhood&amp;rsquo;s map to navigate the world. we fail to recognize. most people opt for a life of very limited honesty and openness and relative closedness, hiding themselves and their maps from the world.
the rewards of the difficult life of honesty and dedication to the truth commensurate the demands.
by exposing my map to other people, i can be challenged and grow as a person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 16:40:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/principles/</guid>
      <description>dont confuse goals with desires
most problems are potential improvements list my problems.
if i cant identify my problems thats because either i lack the skill or lack the will :)
the problems are harsh reality, very painful to look at. so i cope my subconsciously put them out of sight to make them out of mind
i defintely worry about appearing to not have problems than about not achieving my desired results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Mining Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/vi/data-mining-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 13:05:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/vi/data-mining-algorithm/</guid>
      <description>The score functionused to measure the quality of different tree structures is a general miscalassification loss function, defined as $\sum_{i=1}^nC(y(i),\hat{y}(i))$
 $C(y(i),\hat{y}(i))$ is the loss incurred when the class label for the ith data vector, y(i) is predicted by the tree to be $\hat{y}(i)\ne y(i)$  cross-validation  partitions the training data into a subset for building the tree then estimates the misclassifcation rate on the remaining validation subset. this partitioning is repeated multiple times on different subsets and the misclassfication rates are then averaged to yield a cross-validation estimate of how well a tree of a particular size will perform on new, unseen data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PS tldr</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/ps-cmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 19:22:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/ps-cmd/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Setup</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/quote/python-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 20:38:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/quote/python-setup/</guid>
      <description>just found out that both my pip and pip3 are in the same location</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Command</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/article/top-command/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 16:58:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/article/top-command/</guid>
      <description>Linux memory types There are three types of memory, and one is optional.
 physical memory, a limited resource where code and data must reside when executed or referenced. optional swap file: where modified (dirty) memory can be saved and later retrieved if too many demands are made on physical memory big boy virtual memory: unlimited resource intended to   abstraction: free from physical memory addresses/limits isolation: every process in a separate address space sharing: single mapping can serve multiple needs flexibility: assign a virtual address to a file  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles of Data Mining</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/note/principles-of-data-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 11:08:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/note/principles-of-data-mining/</guid>
      <description>Chapter 1 Introduction is an interdisciplinary exercise, can be thought of as statistics, database, or machine learning problem.
from observational datasets to find unsuspected relations and to summarize the data in novel ways
deals with data that have already been collected for some purpose other than the data mining analysis. This is different from statistics, which data are often colleted by using efficient strategies to answer specific answers.
Models and Patterns Include linear equations, rules, clusters, graphs, tree structures, and recurrent patterns in time series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Sleep</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/article/why-we-sleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 22:26:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/article/why-we-sleep/</guid>
      <description>Sleep rhythm This is entirely dependent on your genetics.
Melatonin Melatonin helps regulate the timing of when sleep occurs by systemically signalling that it&amp;rsquo;s time to sleep. It, however, does not play a significant part in sleeping itself but only</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Idleness</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/note/idleness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 09:16:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/note/idleness/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Core</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/article/core/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 20:25:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/article/core/</guid>
      <description>Mình là một người eccentric, và mình biết điều đó. Tính cách đó chỉ thường mang lại cho mình bao nhiều điều phiền toái. Mình khinh thường mình và sự căm ghét những thứ giới hạn bản thân mình vào một khuôn khổ. Khuôn khổ rõ ràng là một từ trung tính, chắc chắn không ai tệ hơn khi bị người khác bỏ vào khuôn khổ. Họ sẽ chỉ cảm thấy tồi tệ hơn thôi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cancel Culture</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/article/cancel-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 13:36:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/article/cancel-culture/</guid>
      <description>Cancel culture - văn hóa loại trừ không loại trừ bất cứ ai</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Class War</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/note/class-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 13:26:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/note/class-war/</guid>
      <description>Excerpts from American Affairs&#39; The Real Class War. Note that this post is literally me taking notes (more like copying verbatim) of what the author wrote and I have absolutely no rights to the material provided. Don&amp;rsquo;t @ me.
 The working class has experienced economic stagnation and precarity, and even life expectancy in the US, as well as ower family stability and civic engagement. Social mobility has declined, while inequality has widened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the nature of Death</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/quote/lucretius/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 17:06:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/quote/lucretius/</guid>
      <description>You, even while you still have life and light, are as good as dead: you squander the greater part of your time in sleep; you snore when awake; you never stop daydreaming; you are burdened with a mind disturbed by grundless fear; and often you cannot discover what is wrong with you, when, like some drunken wretch, you are buffeted with countless cares on every side and drift along aimlessly in utter bewilderement of mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boredom</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/boredom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 17:46:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/boredom/</guid>
      <description>This blog is written for my Gen Z/millenial friends out there.
Imagine a typical school day. You wake up, turn off the alarm. The next thing you do, instinctively, is to check your social media.
After all, man&amp;rsquo;s search for happiness might just be man&amp;rsquo;s search for stimuli.
&amp;ldquo;A certain amount of boredom is essential to a happy life.&amp;rdquo;
Kant&amp;rsquo;s notion of the sublime - our own insignificance in the universe around us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I feel</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/cycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 16:30:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/cycle/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s meta, but I feel like no matter I do, I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to feel like how I want to feel.
Not that I have achieved a lot and feel empty afterwards. Full disclaimer, I have not achieved a single thing that I wanted to do this year. It&amp;rsquo;s sad and pathetic but it&amp;rsquo;s also enlightening, I guess.
It&amp;rsquo;s enlightening in a way that most people I&amp;rsquo;ve met feel this way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limbic Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/limbic-manipulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 15:50:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/limbic-manipulation/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t speak for other countries, but Vietnamese youth have been growing up bombarded with anti-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>on Lee Kuan Yew</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/funny-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 11:45:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/funny-thing/</guid>
      <description>I found myself thinking about what Lee Kuan Yew had to say about many things a lot recently. While I know close to nothing about him, I can imagine that most of his thoughts and actions stemmed from a systemic and practical approach.
I remember reading him stating that while he takes a certain liking to some ideas, he is only interested in what works in real life. This Machiavellian approach to problems reminds me of one of Charlie Munger&amp;rsquo;s lessons in life: avoid extremely intense ideology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ah Here We Go Again</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/ah-here-we-go-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 18:22:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/ah-here-we-go-again/</guid>
      <description>Hello world. Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m going to try to blog again. From my experience from past attempts, I can&amp;rsquo;t keep up with writing essays if I only treat it as a &amp;lsquo;feels good&amp;rsquo; activity when I procrastinate. Now that I know better, I will actually put self-imposed deadlines to churn out content for this blog.
Who knows what to make of this decision. I&amp;rsquo;m in part hopeful that I will try to do my research and write interesting articles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/dl/l3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/dl/l3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/overconfidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/overconfidence/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/problems/</guid>
      <description>all my problems be precise in specifying my problem very poor work habits (react randomly to the stuff that comes at me, cant bring my self to do the statuff that i need to do but dont like to do)
i don&amp;rsquo;t pay any attention to my belongings
i dont pay enough attention at school
my place is really messy
there are days where I don&amp;rsquo;t and can&amp;rsquo;t do anything</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/archives/</guid>
      <description>archives</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/search/</guid>
      <description>search</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
