<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>books on baoqdau</title>
    <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/categories/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in books on baoqdau</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 15:25:22 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.banhtrang.me/categories/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mastery</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 15:25:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/learn/mastery/</guid>
      <description>By nature, we humans shrink from anything that seems possibly painful or overtly difficult. We bring this natural tendency to our practice of any skill. Once we grow dept at some aspect of this skill, generally one that comes more easily to us, we prefer to practice this element over and over. Our skill becomes lopsided as we avoid our weaknesses. Knowing that in our practice we can let down our guard, since we are not being watched or under pressure to perform, we bring to this a kind of dispersed attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defining Decade</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/defining-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 14:45:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/defining-decade/</guid>
      <description>resilient people are usually very likeable. clients with the toughest family backgrounds know the least about how to get what they want in love.
why people choose cohabitation women want better access to love. men want easier access to sex.
experiences   high school and our twenties are the only time when we have the most self-defining memories
  adolescence is the time of our first attempt to form life stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>on Lee Kuan Yew</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/funny-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 11:45:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/en/post/funny-thing/</guid>
      <description>I found myself thinking about what Lee Kuan Yew had to say about many things a lot recently. While I know close to nothing about him, I can imagine that most of his thoughts and actions stemmed from a systemic and practical approach.
I remember reading him stating that while he takes a certain liking to some ideas, he is only interested in what works in real life. This Machiavellian approach to problems reminds me of one of Charlie Munger&amp;rsquo;s lessons in life: avoid extremely intense ideology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
