<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifestyles on BaoQDau</title>
    <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/lifestyle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lifestyles on BaoQDau</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 23:18:53 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.banhtrang.me/lifestyle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tidy</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/lifestyle/tidy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 23:18:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/lifestyle/tidy/</guid>
      <description>discarding all at once intensely and completely tidy in the right order  do not even think of putting things away until i have finished the process of discarding
visualize my destination imagine what it would be like to live in a clutter free space
 visualization aid: look at interior decorating magazines
the fuck this is pseudodeep why i want to design my home that way. after a few rounds of recursive quasi-scientific soul searching im supposed to find out that the point of doing this is to be happy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lift</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/lifestyle/lift/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 23:54:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/lifestyle/lift/</guid>
      <description> best 3 chest exercises: bench press incline dumbbell, remember to bring the dumbbells together
cardio  jumping jacks burpees bicycles ins outs open close shoulder to shoulder high knees  shoulder  reverse peck deck: side lateral raises seated overhead press  10 reps min
leg  smith machines: normal + chair squat + backward squat preacher shrimp dance step on one plate, weights on shoulder, squat down then stand up in the opposite direction smith machine calf raises, with plates 15 lunge while criss crossing kettlebells smith machine jumping lunge push smith machine with balls on your feet one legged squat jump over bench criss crossing on bench   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minigoal</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/lifestyle/goalpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 16:31:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/lifestyle/goalpost/</guid>
      <description>Most important: track how I spend my time digitally fix arbtt and see where I am on the productivity scale brother Completely stop using Tiktok yikes
stop playing mobile games now the question is. what am i going to do next. question  when do i play games? only when i get home. why? is it because my house has a relaxational aspect to it? now how do I stop compulsively gaming?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>