<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on BaoQDau</title>
    <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on BaoQDau</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 16:30:41 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.banhtrang.me/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What I feel</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/post/cycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 16:30:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/post/cycle/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s meta, but I feel like no matter I do, I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to feel like how I want to feel.
Not that I have achieved a lot and feel empty afterwards. Full disclaimer, I have not achieved a single thing that I wanted to do this year. It&amp;rsquo;s sad and pathetic but it&amp;rsquo;s also enlightening, I guess.
It&amp;rsquo;s enlightening in a way that most people I&amp;rsquo;ve met feel this way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>on Lee Kuan Yew</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/post/funny-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 11:45:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/post/funny-thing/</guid>
      <description>I found myself thinking about what Lee Kuan Yew had to say about many things a lot recently. While I know close to nothing about him, I can imagine that most of his thoughts and actions stemmed from a systemic and practical approach.
I remember reading him stating that while he takes a certain liking to some ideas, he is only interested in what works in real life. This Machiavellian approach to problems reminds me of one of Charlie Munger&amp;rsquo;s lessons in life: avoid extremely intense ideology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ah Here We Go Again</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/post/ah-here-we-go-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 18:22:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/post/ah-here-we-go-again/</guid>
      <description>Hello world. Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m going to try to blog again. From my experience from past attempts, I can&amp;rsquo;t keep up with writing essays if I only treat it as a &amp;lsquo;feels good&amp;rsquo; activity when I procrastinate. Now that I know better, I will actually put self-imposed deadlines to churn out content for this blog.
Who knows what to make of this decision. I&amp;rsquo;m in part hopeful that I will try to do my research and write interesting articles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/post/overconfidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/post/overconfidence/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>