<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bao Dau on BaoQDau</title>
    <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/author/bao-dau/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bao Dau on BaoQDau</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 23:18:53 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.banhtrang.me/author/bao-dau/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tidy</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/lifestyle/tidy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 23:18:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/lifestyle/tidy/</guid>
      <description>discarding all at once intensely and completely tidy in the right order  do not even think of putting things away until i have finished the process of discarding
visualize my destination imagine what it would be like to live in a clutter free space
 visualization aid: look at interior decorating magazines
the fuck this is pseudodeep why i want to design my home that way. after a few rounds of recursive quasi-scientific soul searching im supposed to find out that the point of doing this is to be happy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 2</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/dl/l2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 14:20:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/dl/l2/</guid>
      <description>2 sets of books. fastbooks to learn. the other for experiment
dog cat dataset  tags contain dog and cat breeds create category: classification regression: predict one or more numeric quantities?  different applications  diagnosing viruses  terminology  mostly in the book  valid_pct: take a portion of the training dataset and put it asidefor testing purpose
 avoid overfitting
 cnn_learner(,(resnet34: resnet architecture, 34 layers, good for image recognition), metrics=error_rate, epoch: what we call when we look at every single image once?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles of Data Mining</title>
      <link>https://blog.banhtrang.me/note/principles-of-data-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 11:08:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.banhtrang.me/note/principles-of-data-mining/</guid>
      <description>Chapter 1 Introduction is an interdisciplinary exercise, can be thought of as statistics, database, or machine learning problem.
from observational datasets to find unsuspected relations and to summarize the data in novel ways
deals with data that have already been collected for some purpose other than the data mining analysis. This is different from statistics, which data are often colleted by using efficient strategies to answer specific answers.
Models and Patterns Include linear equations, rules, clusters, graphs, tree structures, and recurrent patterns in time series.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>